Guide to the Kennedy Assassination Collection, 1963-1969.
Kennedy Assassination Collection, 1963-1969
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Kennedy Assassination Collection, 1963-1969.
6461.
9 items and .6 cubic ft.
Newspapers articles, photographs, books.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Newspapers and magazines reporting on the assassination of President John F. Kennedy and Robert F. Kennedy.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Newspapers and magazines reporting on the assassination of President John F. Kennedy and Robert F. Kennedy, including the Knickerbocker News, Albany, N.Y. (Nov. 22, 1963); the Ithaca Journal (Nov. 22, 23, 25, 1963, June 5-6, 1968); the New York Times (Nov. 23-25, 1963; Sept. 28, 1964); the Schenectady Gazette (Nov. 25, 1963, Nov. 26, 1963); the New York Herald Tribune (Nov. 24, 26, Dec. 1, 1963); the Washington Evening Star (June 5-8, 1968) and the Washington Post (June 6-10, 1968). Also the New York Times Magazine (Dec. 1, 1963); Time Magazine (Nov. 29, 1963); the Reporter (Dec. 5 and 19, 1963); Look (JFK Memorial Book, Kennedy and His Family in Pictures, and Robert Kennedy Memorial Book); Newsweek (Nov. 28, Dec. 2, 9, 1963 and June 17, 1968); the New Yorker (Nov. 30, 1963); Saturday Evening Post (Dec. 14, 1963); Life Magazine (Nov. 29, Dec. 6, 13, 1963, Oct. 2, 1964 and two special editions); U.S. News and World Report (Dec. 2, 1963); The Torch is Passed produced by the Associated Press; a memorial booklet produced by the Washington Star; and a book produced.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963--Assassination.; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968--Assassination.
Subjects:
Press and politics.; United States--History--1961-1969--Press coverage.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- John F. Kennedy and Robert F. Kennedy Assassinations
  - Newspapers
    - Ithaca Journal, Nov. 22-23, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Ithaca Journal, June 5-6, 1968 (Box 1)
    - New York Times, Nov. 23-26, 1963 (Box 1)
    - New York Times, Sept. 28, 1964 (Box 1)
    - New York Herald, Nov. 24, 1963 (Box 1)
    - New York Herald, Dec. 1, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Evening Star, June 5-8, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Washington Post, June 6-8 and 10, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Additional newspapers (Folder 1)
  - Magazines
    - Life special editions: "The Kennedys" and "JFK Memorial" (Box 1)
    - Life, Nov. 29, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Life, 1963-12-01 (Box 1)
    - Life, Dec. 6, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Life, Oct. 2, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Life, June 14, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Life, Aug. 1, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Look: JFK Memorial Book, Kennedy and his Family in Pictures and edition on Robert Kennedy (Box 1)
    - Look, June 25, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Look, March 4, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Newsweek, Nov. 28, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Newsweek, Dec. 2, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Newsweek, Dec. 9, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Newsweek, June 17, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Time, Nov. 29, 1963 (Box 1)
    - U.S. News and World Report, Dec. 2, 1963 (Box 1)
    - New Yorker, Nov. 30, 1963 (Box 1)
    - The Reporter, Dec. 5, 1963 (Box 1)
    - The Reporter, Dec. 19, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Saturday Evening Post, Dec. 14, 1963 (Box 1)
    - The New York Times Magazine, Nov. 15, 1964 (Box 1)
    - The New York Times Magazine, 1963-12-01 (Box 1)
    - Washington Star's memorial booklet on JFK (Box 1)
    - Associated Press - The Torch is Passed about JFK (Box 1)
    - Washington Daily News production: Four Days about JFK (Box 1)